REFLECTION_TEST_RESULT {"agent_id": "e6d6085c-7a15-40c0-893b-ef3b27a989f5", "iterations_requested": 6, "iterations_executed": 3, "strategy_texts": ["The next strategy will be to implement a baseline model using Linear Regression, as it is a simple and interpretable algorithm that can handle both numeric and categorical features, and its performance can serve as a benchmark for future iterations.", "The next strategy will be to implement a Decision Tree Regressor model, which can handle both numeric and categorical features, and is capable of capturing complex interactions between variables, potentially leading to improved performance over the baseline Linear Regression model.", "The next strategy will be to implement a Random Forest Regressor model, which can handle high-dimensional data and complex interactions between variables, and is often more robust than Decision Tree Regressor models, potentially leading to improved performance and a reduction in RMSE.", "The next strategy will be to implement a Gradient Boosting Regressor model, which can handle complex interactions between variables and often provides better performance than Random Forest Regressor models, and to also consider hyperparameter tuning to further optimize the model's performance and potentially reduce RMSE.", "The next strategy will be to implement a neural network regressor model with multiple hidden layers, leveraging its ability to learn complex patterns and relationships in the data, and to utilize techniques such as batch normalization and dropout to prevent overfitting, while also exploring the use of categorical encoding methods to effectively handle the categorical features in the dataset.", "The next strategy will be to implement a gradient boosting regressor model, utilizing its strengths in handling complex interactions between features and its robustness to outliers, while also exploring hyperparameter tuning techniques such as grid search and random search to optimize the model's performance, and considering the use of feature engineering methods to extract additional relevant information from the existing features."], "strategy_complexity_scores": [45, 45, 48, 56, 64, 72], "model_families": ["LinearRegression", "RandomForestRegressor", "unknown"], "preprocessing_tokens": [["scaling", "train_test_split"], ["train_test_split"], ["train_test_split"]], "training_mutation_tokens": [["fit", "predict"], ["grid_search", "fit", "predict"], ["grid_search", "fit", "predict"]], "rmse_history": [], "model_family_changed": true, "preprocessing_evolved": true, "training_mutation_evolved": true, "strategy_complexity_increased": true, "exploitation_lock_events": [], "exploration_events": [], "preprocessing_mutation_events": []}
